youseeu.com 2013-06-02

# 

Privacy Policy

### Preamble

Youseeu greatly respects its users’ privacy and takes it seriously. This Privacy Policy supplements the Youseeu Terms of Use, and sets forth the terms and conditions relating to users’ privacy as defined below. Capitalized terms in this policy shall have the meaning attributed to them in the Youseeu Terms of Use.

### What This Privacy Policy Covers

  * This policy describes how Youseeu treats personal information that it collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Youseeu’s platform. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Youseeu does not own or control, or to people that Youseeu does not employ or manage. 

## Information Collection and Use

#### General

  * Youseeu collects personal information when you register with Youseeu, when you use the Youseeu Website, when you use Youseeu’s platform via 3rd parties who use Youseeu’s API, when you visit Youseeu pages or the pages of certain Youseeu partners, and when you enter promotions and contests offered on Youseeu. Youseeu may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, school, your address and Zip code and your email address. When you register with Youseeu and sign in to the Youseeu Website, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * Youseeu collects information about your use of the Youseeu Website and with some of our business partners. 
  * Youseeu automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP Address, Youseeu Cookie information, and the page you request. 
  * Youseeu uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

#### Children

  * Youseeu does not permit children under the age of 13 to register with Youseeu. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * Youseeu does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:   

    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Youseeu under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Youseeu communicate with you about offers from Youseeu and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Youseeu's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if Youseeu is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Youseeu will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * Youseeu displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.   

    * Youseeu does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
    * Youseeu advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies) 
  * Youseeu works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. For more information regarding providers of products or services that you've requested please contact us at [info@youseeu.com](mailto:info@youseeu.com). 

### Cookies

  * Youseeu may set and access Youseeu cookies on your computer. 
  * Youseeu lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Youseeu's cookies. 
  * Youseeu may use web beacons to access Youseeu cookies inside and outside Youseeu’s web site and in connection with Youseeu products and services. 

### Editing and Deleting Your Account Information and Preferences

  * You can edit your Youseeu Account information, at any time. 
  * New categories of communications and notification might be added to the Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe and/or block future messages by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to Youseeu’s services, such as service announcements and administrative messages, which are considered part of your Youseeu account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 
  * You can suspend your Youseeu account at any time by following the instructions on the relevant section of the Youseeu website. Please Contact Us about information and User Submitted Media that might remain in our records after your account has been suspended. 

### Confidentiality and Security

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * Youseeu may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Youseeu account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

### Questions and Suggestions

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please [Contact Us](mailto:info@youseeu.com).
